其他人在西雅图的时候  我们俩在伦敦
You and I were in London when the other guys spent time in Seattle.
我在跟暴力犯罪数据库的詹妮通话
I'm on the phone right now with Jennie from VICAP
看那种犯罪手法有没有被模仿过
to see if that particular M.O. has ever been duplicated.
我在线
Yeah, I'm still here.
西雅图  九月初
Uh, it would be Seattle, early September.
对
Right.
不要发邮件  你能传真过来吗
No, not email. Can you fax it?
传真  是的
Fax, yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来是模仿了
I take that as a yes.
在模仿沉默者案件之前
Before he copied the silencer case,
他在西雅图  就在施虐者案件侦破后的几周
he was in Seattle weeks after they solved the sadist.
看看传真来了没  她把案件发过来了
Go check the fax machine. She just sent you that replicated case.
-谢谢  宝贝  -不客气
- Thanks, baby girl. - Yeah. Yeah.
我总算做对事情了
Ok. I did something right.